RICK: Learning to fly this thing,
Morty, is gonna be really liberating.
You know, you're gonna be free to
go on all kinds of errands for me.
- Cool.
- See that planet right there?
Don't fly too close
to that planet.
Someone will come out and try
to wash your windshield.
[Ringtone plays]
Hold on.
[Cellphone beeps]
Yeah?
Yeah, I have it.
Where do you want to meet?
All right, cool.
[Cellphone beeps]
All right, Morty,
lesson's over.
We got some business
to attend to
a few light minutes
south of here.
Oh, you still use
south in space?
Whoa! Jesus, Jerry!
What the hell are you doing here?!
What are you talking about?
We agreed a boy's father
should be present
- when he's learning to drive.
- I guess I remember that.
Wow. And you've just been back
there this whole time?
Amazing.
Well, we don't have time to
take him to earth, Morty.
Head for 3924917.
Cool!
[Laughs]
Looks like I'm coming along
for an adventure!
Yep.
[Sighs]
- This is where we're going?
- Nope.
This is.
You can park in a handicap
spot, Morty.
Anything with less than eight limbs
is considered disabled here.
Well, look at this fella.
Aren't you handsome?
Thank you.
[Chuckles]
- I'm Jerry.
- Oh, I know you are.
Did you come here in a
spaceship?
I'm traveling with my son and
father-in-law.
W-wait. Are they coming?
Oh, they'll be back soon.
What?!
I don't know how this works!
Help me!
What the hell?!
I know, right?
Oh, what the hell?!
MORTY: Jerryboree!?
You created a day care for my
dad?
Are you kidding?
I wish I had this idea.
Well, I did have this idea,
but I wish I was the version
of me that owned it.
That guy's rich.
Don't forget to check the
reason for your drop-off.
Trust me, Morty, I've heard
stories from other Ricks.
Jerrys don't tend to last five
minutes off of earth.
This is a totally unregistered
cross-temporal asteroid.
Here, they can romp and play
with other Jerrys.
He couldn't be safer.
Hey, Morty, hang on to this.
That number's your dad.
If you lose it, we're not
gonna be able to get him back.
♪
Sync and corrections by XhmikosR
www.addic7ed.com
[Electricity crackles]
♪
- Okay, wait here.
- I want to come with.
Don't come with.
It's boring.
It's [Belches]...
it's business stuff.
What kind of business do you
do in a garage?
You know, this seems
a little shady.
Right, yeah, like nothing
shady ever happened
in a fully furnished office?
You ever hear about
Wall Street, Morty?
Y-you know what those guys do
in their fancy boardrooms?
They take their balls and they
dip them in cocaine
and wipe them all
over each other.
You know, grandpa goes around,
and he does his business in public,
because grandpa isn't shady.
Aw, crap.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, Rick!
[Laughs]
Here you go 3,000 flerbos.
Do you have the weapon?
C-can we please?
This is my grandson, Morty.
Oh, hi, Morty.
I'm Krombopulos Michael.
I'm an assassin.
I buy guns from your grandpa.
[Groans]
Here. Go away.
Ooh! Yeah, this looks deadly.
So, this shoots antimatter?
My target can't be killed with
regular matter.
Nice to meet you, Morty.
Listen, if you ever need anybody
murdered, please give me a call.
- I'm very discreet.
- You're g-giving him a card?!
I have no code of ethics.
I will kill anyone, anywhere
children, animals, old people
doesn't matter.
I just love killing.
You sell weapons to killers
for money?
[Groans] You've got what the
intergalactic call
a very planetary mind-set, Morty.
It's more complicated out here.
These are flerbos.
Do you understand what two
humans can accomplish
- with 3,000 of these?
- Uh, what?
An entire afternoon
at Blips and Chitz!
Oh, this place is the best.
It's got beer, games, prizes,
and you can never
tell what time it is.
You sold a gun to a murderer
so you could play video games?!
Yeah, sure, I mean, if you spend
all day shuffling words around,
you can make anything
sound bad, Morty.
Here, check this out.
[Coin drops]
[Whoosh!]
Aah!
[Breathing heavily]
Roy, what's wrong?
I had a nightmare.
I was with an old man.
He put a helmet on me.
It's just a fever.
Get some sleep.
I don't want you missing
school on Monday.
[Bell rings]
MAN: I want you kids to look
around you today
and think about your future.
Now is the time in your life
when anything is possible.
ANNOUNCER: Spiraling
perfectly!
It's gonna be caught
by Roy Parsons!
Roy Parsons is at the 20!
Now he's at the 10!
Nothing can stop Roy
"the Rocket"!
Touchdown!
[Cheers and applause]
I just think it's time
to get realistic.
Have you talked to my father
about the carpet store?
Roy?
[Sighs]
[Cellphone rings]
Had we caught it sooner well,
hindsight is 20/20, Roy.
What's important is that we
move quickly.
[Monitor beeps]
[Weakly] I'm not ready to die.
You're not going to.
- Yeah! Whoo!
- Yeah!
Hey, thanks for
the carpet, Roy.
MAN: Hey, Roy, you pulled
those persian off-white shags
for the clearance sale?
Whoa. Sh shit!
[Bones crack]
Oh!
[Beeping]
Whoa!
What the hell?!
W-w-where am I?!
- What in the hell?!
- 55 years. Not bad, Morty.
You kind of wasted
your 30s, though,
with that whole
bird-watching phase.
- Where's my wife?!
- Morty, you were just playing a game.
It's called "Roy".
Snap out of it. Come on.
I'm Morty. You're Rick.
Hey! You sold a gun to a guy
that kills people!
Look at this you beat cancer,
and then you went back to work
at the carpet store?
Boo!
D-don't dodge the issue, Rick!
Selling a gun to a hit man is the
same as pulling the trigger!
It's also the same
as doing nothing.
If Krombopulos Michael wants
someone dead,
there's not a lot anyone can
do to stop him.
That's why he does
it for a living.
Now excuse me. It's time to
thrash your "Roy" score.
You know, you could stop this
killing from happening, Rick!
You know, you did a bad thing
selling that gun,
but you could undo
it if you wanted.
Uh-huh, yeah, that's the difference
between you and me, Morty.
- I never go back to the carpet store.
- Holy shit!
This guy's taking Roy off the grid!
[All gasp]
This guy doesn't have a social
security number for Roy!
[All murmuring]
Hi. I'm sorry.
I think there was a
misunderstanding.
I'm an adult and would like to
go home, please.
Well, of course.
Right through that tube.
Unbelievable.
You're doing great.
I know how to crawl in a tube.
[Sighs]
Come on.
Oh.
This is harder than it looks.
Whoa!
- Marco?
- Polo!
[Laughs]
Marco?
Come find me.
You guys are enjoying this?
Don't you feel a little
patronized?
How so?
- Jerry!
- Beth.
Oh, come on.
This is ridiculous.
I love you, Jerry.
Aw, Beth.
Who wants to come watch
"midnight run"
with director's commentary on?
- Yeah!
- Definitely.
First one there gets to adjust
the picture setting!
[Gasps] The factory tint
setting is always too high!
Out of my way.
The tint setting is always too high.
[Mid-tempo music plays]
♪
[Smooches]
Oh, boy.
Here I go killing again.
Aah!
Arh!
[Neck snaps]
Aah!
[Scanner chirping]
[Neck snaps]
[Warbling]
You have arrived at
Krombopulos Michael.
Your destination is below.
We're all out of off-white
Persian.
Oh, man!
W-w-what have I done?!
- Drop the gun.
- You don't understand!
- This guy was gonna kill someone!
- I guess that makes two of us.
[Rifle charging]
Aah!
What are you doing, Morty?
This is a galactic
federation outpost!
Look, I don't have time to
tell you my entire backstory,
but grandpa and government
don't get along.
He saved my life.
- What?
- Huh?! Whoa!
Are you Krombopulos Michael's
target?
W-what's your name?
My kind has no use for names.
I communicate through what
you call "Jessica's feet"
no, "telepathy".
Oh, good job, Morty.
Y-you killed my best customer,
but you saved a
mind-reading fart.
I like this name fart.
Morty, would you kindly
release me
by pulling that lever to the
left of my cell?
I am in great pain.
Morty, don't do it.
Morty...
Morty, you idiot.
[Alarm blaring]
Oh, crap.
Let's get you out of here!
We can't get him out of here.
He's gaseous.
He's not gonna make it through
a portal, Morty.
Well, then, I guess we're all
getting in the car.
- Right, uh...
- Fart.
- No! Just just get in the car!
- Morty, come on.
I want to go back to
Blips and Chitz.
I don't want to deal with this.
Rick, you've been
clear on the fact
that you don't want to help,
so just go away.
More are coming.
Screw this.
I'm out.
[Engine sputtering]
Whoa!
Come on, come on!
Get out of the vehicle made of
garbage or we will open fire!
[Engine sputtering]
Um, um, um, um!
Open fire!
Aah!
Stupid-ass, fart-saving,
carpet-store mother[bleep].
Move!
Wait, did you [bleep]
with my seat settings?
[Motor whirring]
More are coming.
Rick!
Yeah, yeah.
Your geldon convertor is
pretty dinged up.
That's because my grandson
drives like a male Obravadian.
Yeah, I said it some
stereotypes are based in fact.
Actually, it's because of
years of neglect.
You really need to respect
your gears, Rick.
To you, they're just
wheels with teeth,
but in my culture, wars have
been fought--
So I've heard.
Just fix it.
I don't think the gromflamites
can track us now,
but it looks like we're gonna
be here for a while.
Or, you know, if you still have
that gun K. Michael dropped,
we could finish the job
and go home.
- You do understand I'm telepathic, right?
- I'm being polite.
Rick, we're taking him back
where he belongs.
Oh, yeah? Where's that?
[Belches]
Are you going on a quest to
find he who smelt it?
I came here accidentally
through a wormhole
located in what you call
"Get out of my head, fart.
I know you're in here.
La-la-la-la".
No, in what you call the
Promethean Nebula.
Oh, great. Just a hop, skip,
and an 800-light-year jump.
You know, you can leave
anytime you want, Rick.
Whatever you want to do,
you little punk-ass little bitch.
Thank you, Morty.
You are not like other
carbon-based life-forms.
You put the value of all life
above your own.
It's how things should be.
It's how they could be.
I could not agree more.
♪ The worlds can
be one together ♪
♪ Cosmos without hatred ♪
♪ Stars like diamonds
in your eyes ♪
♪ The ground can be space ♪
♪ Space, space,
space, space ♪
♪ With feet marching
towards a peaceful sky ♪
♪ All the moon men want
things their way ♪
♪ But we make sure
they see the sun ♪
♪ Goodbye, moon men ♪
♪ You say goodbye,
moon men ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
Shut the [bleep] up
about moon men!
This isn't a musical number.
This is a [bleep] operation.
We got to be cool and [bleep]
lay low.
[Clicks, computer chimes]
[Laughing]
Duck, duck, birdie?
[Laughs]
That's very funny!
Here comes another funny.
[Clicks, computer chimes]
[Laughs]
Oh, this place is great.
I almost wish I could stay
longer than one day.
You just might.
W-what do you mean?
These are the Jerrys whose Ricks
and Mortys never came back.
They live here now.
Uh.
[Rock music plays]
[Engine revs]
[Tires screech]
[Dramatic music plays]
No gear-turnings as of yet in
the curious case
of these unidentified
humanoid fugitives,
reportedly at large somewhere
within the gear system.
Son of a...
Why were the gromflamites
holding you prisoner?
What the [bleep] is so
valuable about you?
I am no more valuable
than life itself.
However, I am able to alter
the composition of atoms,
like this.
[Electricity crackling]
That was oxygen.
I added 71 protons to it.
Terrific.
The fart that pooped gold.
No wonder every cop in the
system is looking for us.
Any species that gets
ahold of this thing
is gonna use it to
take over the galaxy.
You know how inconvenient
that's gonna be to my work?
[Sirens wailing]
Somebody dropped
the dime on us.
Gearhead!
I'm sorry, Rick.
The reward on your
head is too high.
And like you always say,
you got to look out
for number one.
Number one is me, asshole!
You're supposed to be my friend!
Friend?! Do you even
know my real name?
It's Revolio Clockberg Junior.
I belong to an entire species
of gear people.
Calling me "gearhead" is like calling
a Chinese person "Asia face".
No! Not twigs!
[Groans]
[Muffled screaming]
Two things I want to make
clear to everybody in this room
never betray me,
and it's time to go.
[Muffled screaming]
Nobody move!
Oh, my god.
Are those...
♪
[Grunts]
[Screams]
Hey, Morty, remember
when you said
selling a gun was as bad as
pulling the trigger?
How do you feel about all
these people
that are getting killed today
because of your choices?
I did the right thing, Rick!
- Tell that to gearhead's gearsticles.
- You did that!
Wrong! I'd be playing "Roy"
right now.
At a certain point,
my hands are tied, Morty.
[Sighs]
I can't believe Rick did this.
- This is the eighth to the last straw.
- Ante up.
You know what?
Screw it!
I have a better
gamble for you guys.
I say we escape.
If you want to leave, you can
just go out the front door.
You think we're kept here
against our will?
That would be illegal.
But if you can leave, then why
are you still here?
Same reason as you.
We're Jerrys.
I'm leaving.
Okay, then.
That was always allowed.
♪
Morty, take the wheel!
Whoa!
Geez!
Damn it, Morty!
Who taught you to
fly this thing?
[Laughs] I'm kidding.
I know that's on me.
Um, Rick!
Shit.
Well, I guess this is it.
Morty, crack the window.
I wonder why Greg is always so
critical of my girlfriend.
Well, he'd probably like to
have me to himself.
That's how friends are.
Or does he want herto himself?
♪ The worlds can
be one together ♪
♪ Cosmos without hatred ♪
♪ Stars like diamonds
in your eyes ♪
My life is a [bleep] joke!
♪ Goodbye, moon men ♪
♪ You say goodbye,
moon men ♪
♪ Goodbye, moon men ♪
All right.
Let's proceed.
Damn.
Can't blame that on the dog.
Talk about silent but deadly.
I-I've seen some nerve gas,
but that this gas got nerve!
[Laughs] You know
what I'm saying?
- Are you done?
- I'll let you know, Morty.
Gone with the wind!
Am I right?!
If you don't like
that one, Morty,
an alt on that could be, like,
if I said "gasablanca"!
All right, I'm done.
Let's get to the
Promethean Nebula,
so my grandson can finish
saving a life!
[Trills]
- Glagga blag blag.
- Um, Earth, please?
[Growls]
Is this...
Do I pay?
Agga blag blag blag!
[Indistinct shouting]
Oh, I'm sorry, sorry!
Ohh.
Hmm.
Mm, hey.
[Hisses]
Aah!
Agga blag blag?
Oh, uh, hey.
What?
- Agga blag!
- Uh, what do you want?
Agga blag blag ohh!
Uh...
[Speaking native language]
[Whimpering]
[Moaning]
[Alarm blaring]
[Wailing in distance]
[Whimpers]
[Shouting in alien language]
Hey.
Are you the one that left?
I get it.
It's a...
it's a hassle out there.
Right?
And who needs that?
- Right?
- Not me.
- Who needs that?
Ho, ho!
Not us.
Uh, who are you?
Oh, excuse me.
Paul Fleischman.
Infinite timelines.
In some of them,
Beth remarries.
- Geez.
- Don't worry.
I treat Beth very well,
and I do not overstep my
bounds with Morty.
Every kid needs a dad,
but there's no replacing you.
Hey, you want to give us a
hand with this?
We're trying to figure out how
to get the sound
coming through the stereo
instead of the TV.
It's very difficult.
Oh! Uh, well, is
there an aux input?
We tried that, but there's two
different colors.
But there's two
[Growls]
The wormhole is 70 of what you
call "meters"
what you call "north" of what
you call "here".
Fine. Morty, take your fart to
his hole and say your goodbyes.
I'm gonna find some fuel and
take a big, fat Morty.
That's my new word for shit
because of today's events.
♪
Here it is.
This should take me
back to my kind.
I'm gonna miss you, um, Fart.
I'm really sorry your name
became fart.
- I will be back soon, Morty.
- Really?
After I return to the others
with this location,
we will be back for your
cleansing.
Um, cleansing?
Carbon-based life is a threat
to all higher life.
To us, you are what you would
call a disease.
Wherever we discover you,
we cure it.
You said yourself that life
must be protected,
even though sacrifice.
You haven't changed your mind
about that.
I can sense your thoughts.
Morty?
Um, before you go,
could you sing a
c-could you sing for me again?
Yes, Morty.
♪ Cosmos without hatred ♪
♪ Diamond stars of
cosmic light ♪
♪ Quasars shine through
endless night ♪
♪ And everything is
one in the beauty ♪
♪ And now we say goodbye ♪
Aah!
[Weakly]
Morty, why? Why?
[Groaning]
Goodbye.
So, did you guys make
out a little bit?
Is he gonna send you
a postcard?
Man, that guy hit the lottery
when he crossed paths with you.
Morty, I know I picked on your
core beliefs
and decision making
a lot today,
but I am glad that you insisted
on getting that fart home.
You know, at least all the
death and destruction
wasn't for nothing, you know?
You miss your fart friend, huh?
Well, I got a little surprise
for you, buddy.
While you were gone,
I found a new wormhole
with millions of beings just
like him on the other side,
and they're all
coming to visit.
What?! Rick, no!
You can't!
Too late, Morty.
The hole's opening.
No, Rick!
You don't understand.
[Farts]
There's there's a lot more
where that came from, too.
[Indistinct conversations]
Hey, hey, bro, how many people
was your Morty responsible for
killing today?
None. We chilled at
Blips and Chitz all day.
Ain't that right, homey?
Darn right, bro!
"Roy" rules!
[Laughter]
Must be nice.
Hey, Morty, there's our Jerry.
Mm! I missed you.
Hey, Rick.
Glad you're safe, Jerry.
- What do you say we go home?
- I'd like that.
Hey, wait.
Uh, do you have 5126?
Uh, I'm not sure.
Morty.
Uh, that's a Blips and Chitz
ticket.
- What?!
- [Scoffs] Way to go, Morty.
Eh, whatever.
- Uh, w-wait. What?
All right.
Come on, Jerry.
♪
Sync and corrections by XhmikosR
www.addic7ed.com
Are you tired of the same
daily droll?
Well, get on over
to Blips and Chitz!
We got, uh, one game.
We got a whole bunch
of games here.
You can we got chabos and flobos,
and you can shoot things!
Get over here!
Play the games!
Uh, use your flerbos
to get tickets!
"Roy 2" just got here.
Get over here at Jitz and
Chitz!
It's the coolest
place in the world.
[Laughs]
Uh, I get to be in the
commercial!