- Bye, mom! Bye, dad!
- Drive carefully!
Have fun, you two.
Yes, we will have as
much fun as possible on our...
Titanic -themed getaway.
Let's lose the 'tude, please.
It's supposed to be romantic.
Speaking of disasters, dad, we
are leaving you in charge, here.
I know, c-can we wrap this up?
Morty and I have some synthetic
laser eels oxidizing in the garage.
Hey, don't blow me off.
I am drawing a line, okay?
Any damage to this house or
these children when we get back,
and... no more
adventures with Morty.
Aw, geez, Rick.
If my mom's the one
who's saying it,
then you know it's pretty
serious this time.
That's right.
Wait. What?
Listen, you have my
word as a caregiver,
everything's gonna be fine.
And if not, like you say, no
more adventures or whatever.
It's like that old song
"blomp blomp-a noop noop
a-noop noop noop".
You guys know that song?
From tiny rogerts?
You never heard of it?
You know, the black effeminate
guy from the '50s?
No-nobody?
A-all right, whatever.
Look, who cares?
Just go on your stupid trip.
Not one thing out of place.
Not a single thing.
Well, we're past the
point of no return.
I'm going to have a party.
Corrections by XhmikosR
www.addic7ed.com
I found jello.
Can you sneak your mom's vodka?
Yes, she does.
I saw it in your laundry room.
Listen, you can't both be in
denial about it.
Okay, bye.
Summer, you can't
throw a party!
Remember what mom said?
Yeah, if anything gets messed up,
you and grandpa Rick get punished.
I'm only a human being, Morty.
Rick, tell summer she
can't have a party!
Uh, summer, you can't
have a party.
Because I'm having a
party, b-I-I-I-itch!
Oh, what?!
Rick, you can't!
What do you mean
you're having a party?
Are some glip glops from the
third dimension going to come
over and play cards or
something?
"Glip glop?"
You're lucky a traflorkian
doesn't hear you say that.
Is that like their n-word?
It's like the n-word
and the c-word had a baby and it
was raised by all the bad words
for Jews.
Listen, I think the three
of us could just, you know,
have a nice time, like
just hanging out, and, you know,
doing a little bonding and --
screw that.
This is my chance to gain some
footing with the cool kids.
That's why you party?
Boy, you really are 17.
Why do you party?
To get wr-wriggedy
wriggedy wrecked, son!
Just keep your Sci-Fi friends
away from my awesome ones.
Yeah, and you keep your awesome
friends away from my canapes.
After dinner, Titanic 2 will
attach to the rail system near
our replica iceberg, and the
hydraulics encased in these
tubes will execute a controlled
sink into the icy depths.
A rail system seems archaic for
an attraction this impressive.
Are you sure the ship will sink?
I can assure you the ship
will sink, as it has a thousand
times before.
It is un-unsinkable.
Ooh!
Look, it's the line
for the bow!
Jerry, I'd love to just kick
back with a Margarita and read.
Do you mind if I skip the whole
"king of the world" bit?
Well, it's not the
"king of the world" bit.
That's Jack and fabrizio.
This is where rose says, "I'm
flying, Jack!" But whatever.
I can be the only
one to do it alone.
Well, what about her?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Would you like to take
my place in line?
I, uh -- I could get into
trouble.
We won't tell.
So...
- You're a Titanic fanatic?
- Oh, yes.
I've worked here
since it opened,
but I've never been
able to participate.
Happy to help... rose.
I love watching bukkake.
I mean, like, I don't know if I
personally would ever do it...
Brad! Hey!
Yo.
Brad is here!
Quick, make my hair look drunk.
Check it out.
Tammy's already drunk.
Cool.
The beacon was activated.
Who is in danger?
Ugh! Grandpa!
Birdperson!
I am pleased there is no
emergency.
Oh, there's an
emergency, all right.
A emergency!
When's the last time you got
laid, 'pers?
It has been a... challenging
mating season for birdperson.
Then it's time to get
your beak wet tonight, playah.
Go have some fun out there
birdp-- bird-- birdperson.
Oh, man, how many
people did you invite, Rick?
Uh... people?
Mm, six.
Yo! What up, my glip glops?!
Oh, man!
Oh!
Y-y-you know there's a garbage,
right?
Hey, uh, what the hell?!
Ooh. That's why you never
invite a floopy doop
and a shmoopy doop
to the same party.
Oh, oh, g--
oh, that's disgusting!
You guys are in my parents' bed!
Oh. Sorry.
I'm not feeling too well.
I just needed to lie
down for a bit.
Oh. Okay.
S-s-sorry.
Oh, my God!
Are you kidding me?!
The thing people don't
realize about the Gear Wars is
that it was never really about
the gears at all.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
No, no, to-totally.
- Rick, you got to stop --
- Morty!
- Have you met gearhead?
- Hey, how's --
Morty here, he -- he would love
to hear all about the Gear Wars.
How familiar are you with the
Gear Wars, exactly?
Uh... Not at all.
Oh, boy.
I envy you.
Okay, it was about
754 years ago...
Oh, hey, Morty!
H-have you -- have you
met my buddy scropon?
Not again, Rick.
That last guy droned on for
20 minutes, you know?
And meanwhile, the whole house
is being destroyed!
Whoa, Morty, this guy's
entire planet was destroyed.
Have a little perspective.
Hey, Rick, squanchy
party, bro!
Aw! Squanchy!
Is there a good place for me
to squanch around here?
Squanchy, you can
squanch wherever you want, man.
- Mi casa es su casa, dawg!
- All right!
I like your squanch!
Uh, Rick, what exactly
is "squanching"?
Morty, listen -- we've
had a lot of really cool
adventures over the last year,
but it's time to relax.
Yeah, if I relax now, there might
not even be any more adventures!
Jesus, Morty, you're
bumming me out.
Can't we just pretend like
everything's fine for a few hours,
enjoy ourselves, and then
worry about all this later?
Yeah, that's easy for
you to say, Rick.
You know, you like not caring
about stuff.
You know, wh-wh-what's in this
for me?
For me?
Jessica.
Knock it off, slow mobius!
Ha ha! Sorry, dude!
I'm just trying to show off my
powers, bro!
I can't believe she's here.
Well, what are you
doing standing here, Morty?
Go. Talk to her.
Tonight, the only adventure you're
on is your cusping manhood.
Oh, Rose.
Whee!
Is that what I think it is?
Yes, every couple gets to
re-create Jack's drowning at the
end of the movie.
It's so romantic.
I can't wait to do
that with Beth.
I don't know, Jerry.
With all due respect, it seems
like your wife may not be that
interested.
Look!
Iceberg, right ahead!
The buffet is now closed.
Uh, sir?
There's not a problem.
What do you mean there's not
a problem?
The guidance system isn't putting
us on a direct collision course.
This ship is about to completely
miss the giant iceberg!
Well, do something!
Steer into it!
I'm trying!
It's too late.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Don't brace yourselves.
No! No!
What happened?!
Their rail system
must have failed.
Oh, my God!
We're not gonna sink!
Totally gonna get
laid tonight.
I like your feathers.
They are designed to attract
the attention of the female.
It's working.
Tammy, I should let you know
I just got out of a highly
intense soul bond with my
previous spirit mate.
I'm not looking to get into a
soul bond.
I'm just looking for...
I believe birdperson can
arrange that.
Hey, Summer, haven't seen you
at flute practice in a while.
Summer, don't tell me you're
friends with her.
Are you kidding me?
I don't even know what she's
doing here.
Whoa. Not cool, summer.
This is a party.
Everybody should be welcome.
Oh, great.
Who invited Abradolph Lincoler?
I thought everyone
was welcome.
It's not the same, Summer.
Lincoler is a crazed maniac --
just a misguided effort of mine
to create a morally neutral
superleader by combining the DNA of
Adolf Hitler and Abraham Lincoln.
Turns out it just adds
up to a lame, weird loser.
Rick, you brought me into
this world, a suffering
abomination tortured by the
duality of its being.
But I shall finally know peace
when I watch the life drain from
your wretched body!
Whoa. What's up, man?
I have no quarrel
with you, boy.
"Boy"?
What's that supposed to mean?
It's just -- l-look, I-I
don't know how you thought I
meant it, but...
Don't look at me, dude.
Look, I'm
half-Abraham Lincoln, so --
So I should get on my knees
and kiss your ass?!
Well, no, but...
- You know?
- What do I know?
That the third reich will reign
for a thousand years?
Leave him alone, Brad.
Stay out of this, Jessica!
Kick his ass, Brad!
Kick his ass!
Brad!
Rick!
I just did you a favor, Morty.
Sorry about all that.
Rick has some really strange
friends.
Ugh! Brad is such a jerk.
He's always trying to prove what
a man he is.
I just want to find somebody
nice and sweet.
Jessica, can I show
you something?
Wow! Look at all this stuff.
Yeah.
This is me and my grandpa Rick's
Sci-Fi workshop.
Check this out.
It's beautiful.
You know, Jessica,
there's something I've always
wanted to tell you.
What's that, Morty?
I think that
you're the most --
No, that -- those weird sounds
coming from the closet over there.
- Oh, my God!
- Aah!
Hey, I'm squanching in here!
Oh, my God!
Oh, that is so disgusting!
Ow! Oh! Oh, crap!
Huh.
Big star in the sky.
Oxygen-rich atmosphere.
Giant testicle monsters.
We'll be fine! Let's party!
♪ Just shake that ass, bitch,
and let me see whatcha got ♪
I swear to God,
Morty, if it weren't for the
fact that everyone's still
having a blast in there,
I would be so furious
with you right now.
Oh, man.
Y-you hear that, Morty?
You really lucked out with
Summer o-on that one.
How are you guys not
freaking out right now?!
T-the whole house is sitting in
another dimension!
I-I mean, w-what the hell are we
supposed to do?!
M-m-mom and dad are
gonna kill us!
- I'm losing it here, Rick!
- Relax, Morty, relax!
It's gonna be fine.
All we have to do is go out and
find us some kalaxian crystals.
Oh, shit, mother [beep]!
Kalaxian crystals, Morty, just a
few miles South of here.
Okay. Let's go, then.
W-w-we got to go get those
crystals right now, Rick.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Morty, Morty, I-I can't go with
you.
I got to hang back and make sure
everything stays cool here, you
know?
I mean, who knows what -- what
if somebody breaks something?
Yeah. Me too.
I should stay.
You guys have any aspirin?
Oh, hey, Morty, this is
perfect!
You can take Lincoler with you.
Hey, man, I'm not going
anywhere.
- I'm injured.
- Shut up, Lincoler.
It's the least you can
do for wrecking the living room.
Yeah!
And, Nancy, you should go, too.
What? Why -- why me?
Because, uh,
you're -- you're so good at
playing the flute.
Sorry for the inconvenience,
folks.
We should resume sinking
shortly.
In the meantime, please, stay on
the ship and enjoy
a complimentary plate of
James Cameronion rings.
Great. Not only is the
ship not sinking,
but now the fourth wall
has been broken.
I am gonna go back to the room
to finish my book.
You should find
that Lucy woman.
But -- but --
You see, Jerry?
May I show you something?
Had everything gone as planned,
this entire area would be
underwater.
I would have liked to see it.
This trip has been a "Titanic"
failure.
Get it?
Ooh!
- Draw me, Jerry.
- Oh, boy.
Lucy, wow.
Uh, this isn't what I had in
mind.
But it's the perfect moment.
We've been dreaming about this
for 16 years.
Um, not like this.
Not -- not with you.
- You are gonna draw me.
- Aah!
Then you're going to
[beep] me in that car over there.
It's weird, 'cause I definitely think
that all men are created equal.
But, at the same time --
Okay!
Um, the crystals should be
really close.
There they are!
Wait. Something's not right.
Get the crystals!
I'll handle the beast!
Prepare to be emancipated from
your own inferior genes!
Summer's gonna like me again.
Lincoler, come on!
Let's get out of here!
Mein journey is over, Morty.
I have something
important to tell you.
♪ And the gears, they turned
for a thousand years ♪
♪ until the dark day that they
stopped ♪
Rick, I got them!
- I got the crystals!
- All right!
- You did it, Morty.
- Rick, wait!
There's something you need to
know.
I couldn't have done it without
Lincoler.
He said that he was really sorry and
that he loves you like a father.
He only wanted you
to accept him,
and he hopes that his final act
would redeem him in your eyes.
He sacrificed himself to save
all of us, Rick.
He died.
Well, at least he
didn't die in vain.
He got these crystals.
And these babies just saved this
lame-ass party!
Wubba, lubba, dub, dub!
Play something.
Somebody, play something.
Wait a minute. What?
♪ Put your right foot forward ♪
♪ and your left foot back ♪
♪ then slide around ♪
♪ like on a nordictrack ♪
♪ move to the left ♪
♪ step to the right ♪
♪ wiggle your elbows, and look ♪
♪ up into the light ♪
♪ it's the, it's the ♪
♪ it's the Rick dance ♪
Slow mobius, hit me
with the clock beam!
♪ It's the, it's the ♪
♪ it's the Rick dance ♪
That's the Rick dance!
All right!
Whoa, man!
What the hell was that?!
I thought those crystals were
supposed to help us get home or
something!
What? No, no, no.
I can get us home whenever I
want to.
But, listen, speaking
of those crystals,
can I get the rest of them?
I'm starting to come down,
Morty.
Crystal kalaxian is a really
strong, but fleeting high.
That's what I think of your
crystals, Rick!
Oh, Morty, you idiot!
Does anybody else have any more
k-lax?
B-birdperson?
Uh, squanchy?
Don't squaunch at me.
All right, everybody,
party is officially over!
Rick, take us home now.
All right, all right, fine,
Morty, you party pooper buzzkill!
Boo, boo! Morty sucks!
Boo! You suck, whatever your
name is.
Boo!
Morty, you're the worst, Morty.
But these gears just started
turnin'.
Almost finished, Jerry?
Uh, almost.
I haven't quite captured your
beautiful eyes.
I'm sure it's good enough.
Move!
Every weekend, Jacks and Roses
have their Titanic experience in
this car, and I
have to mop it up.
The floor drops out to make it
easier.
But now it's my turn.
We're going to get it nice and
steamy in there, and I'm going
to slam my hand on the steam and
leave a nice handprint, and then
you're going to love inside of
me.
No mess. No clean.
Beth!
Bet you're glad I think
kindles are dumb now.
I can't help but feel a little
guilty.
I didn't peg Lucy for a rapist.
What does a rapist
look like exactly, Beth?
Is it a slavic man wearing a
denim jacket with a patchy beard
and the scent of
cheap champagne
wafting over his
blister-pocked lips?
What?
Well, at least you got all this
free stuff.
Should be enough to satisfy your
Titanic Jones for a while.
I'm not going to fit.
Beth, listen to me.
You're going to get out of here.
You're gonna go on, and --
Jerry, just leave the door.
It's not a door, Beth.
- It's debris.
- I don't care.
Just leave it.
Yeah. Okay.
"Cape fear"!
I'm -- I'm doing -- I'm -- I'm going
to do like from "cape fear".
Hey, squanchers!
The party's squanching
on at my place!
Cool.
I'm coming, too.
Uh, no.
You're not squanchy enough for a
squanchy party.
What?
Nancy told us what a bitch
you are.
Guys, seriously.
Nancy?
Summer, you're a bad person.
All you care about is having
popular people like you.
That's not what
Abradolph Lincoler stood for.
Well, I-it was hard to pin down
what he stood for, but it's
certainly not what he died for.
Next time I party, I'm just gonna
focus on getting totally wrecked.
You're so wise.
May I assist you with that?
Uh, sure, yeah.
Thanks.
Morty, do you know what
"wubba lubba dub dub" means?
Uh, that's just Rick's
stupid nonsense catchphrase.
It's not nonsense at all.
In my people's tongue, it means,
"I am in great pain.
Please help me."
Well, I got news for you.
He's saying it ironically.
No, Morty.
Your grandfather is, indeed, in
very deep pain.
That is why he must numb
himself.
Come on, um...
Birdperson.
Come on, birdperson.
Rick's not that complicated.
He's just a huge asshole.
Then why do you care so much
if you are no longer allowed to
continue on your adventures
together?
It appears fate has presented
you with an opportunity to free
yourself of Rick forever.
You know what? You're right.
I shouldn't even care.
This is probably the best thing
that could have happened to me.
I'm sick of having adventures
with Rick.
My people have another saying--
"gubba nub nub doo rah kah".
It means, "whatever lets you
sleep at night".
Guys, mom and dad are, like,
right around the corner.
This is your moment, Morty.
Choose wisely.
Tammy!
Caw!
Wow.
We are so screwed.
- Rick, wake up.
- Huh? What? Wait? What?
What? Stop.
Rick, you got to do
something quick.
My parents are home.
Uh, all -- all right.
All right. Hold -- hold on.
Ahh! So good.
Oh, my God.
They're walking up the driveway.
- Bring me the thing.
- What -- what thing?
The thing. The thing.
The -- the -- it's got, like,
buttons on it and lights on it.
It -- it -- it beeps.
Rick!
That describes everything in
your garage!
Do you mean this?
Summer for for the win.
All right, that should do it.
Whoa!
What did you do?
Uh, s-see for yourself.
Whoa!
Yeah, e-everything's
frozen in time.
Yeah, and slow mobius thinks
he's all that.
- For how long?
- I don't know.
How long do you guys want?
A week? A month?
Can we start cleaning
the house and see how we feel?
- Worst movie ever.
- Dumb.
Ooh, boy, what a
waste of time.
Get it?
You know, 'cause it's frozen.
This has been so much fun.
Hey, Rick.
You know, this whole time, I
haven't once heard you say that
"wubba lubba dub dub" thing that
you usually say.
Don't need to.
I have a new catchphrase.
Oh, yeah?
What -- what's that, Rick?
I love my grandkids.
- Aww.
- Psych!
Just kidding -- my new
catchphrase is, "I don't give a [beep]".
♪ Just shake that ass, bitch,
and let me see whatcha got ♪
♪ just shake that ass, bitch,
Roll credits!
♪ Just shake that a--
Roll the credits! Go!
♪ Just shake that ass
That's the end of season one!
That's the end, mother [beep]!
"I don't give a [beep]" is my
new catchphrase!
[Beep] you!
That's season one! Boom!
Season one up in your face,
mother [beep]!
Yeah!
Revenge.
What?!
Party!
Whoo, baby!
Please, stop!
Hey, brah!
I don't understand.
Are you enjoying this?
Do you like this?
Yeah, you know it, dawg!
Whoo, baby!
Corrections by XhmikosR
www.addic7ed.com