ALL: ♪ Love ♪
♪ Connection ♪
♪ Experience ♪
Yeah, Morty.
♪ Come together ♪
♪ With love, connection,
and experience ♪
- It's my favorite song.
- [Laughing] Oh, yeah.
[Alarm beeps]
Oh, yeah, distress beacon!
[Belches] Yeah, baby!
You're excited about that?
The first rule of
space travel, kids,
is always check out
distress beacons.
9 out of 10 times,
it's a ship full of dead aliens
and a bunch of free shit!
BOTH: Whoa!
1 out of 10 times,
it's a deadly trap,
but I'm ready to
roll those dice.
♪ ♪
Seems like something terrible
happened here.
Yep. Cha-ching.
Oh, yeah, if you find a room full
of eggs, don't shy away from it.
Give one of them a shake.
Those facehuggers are worth
more than this ship.
Uh, what's that?
This'll make the cops write it up
as a looting by the korblocks.
- That's horrible.
- I hear you, man. Cops are racist.
Oh, hey. You're alive.
Thank god.
Can you help us?
Our planet was taken over by
some kind of... entity.
It absorbed the minds
of our people.
We didn't notice until
it was too late.
The people it takes over,
they look like your friends,
your family, your leaders,
but they're not themselves anymore.
They're part of... it.
Then how do you know it didn't
get on the ship with you?
Those two dingdongs seem pretty
calm about the whole thing.
[Both screech]
Hey, no! No, wait! Stop!
[Screaming]
Called it.
[Gurgles]
[Ray gun beeps]
ALL: Hello, Rick.
Long time no see.
Unity?
- Rick?
- Grandpa?
Oh, boy. Uh...
These are my grandkids,
Summer and Morty.
Summer, Morty, this is, uh,
Unity.
We sort of used to, uh... date.
♪ ♪
Sync and corrections by XhmikosR
www.addic7ed.com
[Dog panting]
[Engine hums in distance]
Quite an operation you got
going here, Une.
You're a whole planet now, huh?
After we broke up, I spent some
time wandering through space.
- Then I found this world...
- ...Where I was better able
to focus on my passion for
unification.
- You mean stealing people's bodies?
- Summer, rude.
Why don't you two kids go run
off and play with Unity
while Unity and I do some
catching up.
- Ugh.
- No, wait, Rick,
aren't these people gonna barf
into our mouths and absorb us?
You're guests here on my planet.
You're free to be yourselves.
I've never been any good at
disappointing Rick.
Well, now I'm going to barf.
Come on, Morty.
Jerry, what are you what are
you doing in here?
I'm trying to find our weed
whacker,
'cause our weeds are wack, yo.
But you can't go in the
garage when Rick's not here.
- I "can't"?
- Well, he doesn't like it.
What's he gonna do? Crash rent-free
at his other family's house?
What is that supposed to mean?
Your dad gets to walk all over us
because of your abandonment issues.
He's playing you, shorty.
Oh, stop affecting that stupid
hip-hop dialect.
Stop shifting the cross hairs
to my ironic urban patois
just because your relationship
with your father
is to' up from the flo' up.
[Screeching]
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
Let's just leave.
[Gurgling]
That is a hatch.
Your father put a
hatch in my garage.
You don't know it was him.
Anyway, we're not
supposed to be in here.
Obviously, neither is
whatever's gurgling down there.
[Screech, gurgle]
"World peace achieved."
Nice.
Little weird to publish a paper
about it for yourself, but hey.
So, what's next?
After I become a type-one
civilization,
this world will be invited
into the galactic federation.
Oh, goody.
From there, I'll have access to
countless planets and species.
One by one, I will unify them,
I will become the universe,
and I will be what the
single-minded once called the God.
[Belches] I like that.
Oh, that's pretty sexy.
Hey, listen, where can we get
a drink around here?
Recreational substances were
phased out here.
There's no need for escape from
the self when your world is one.
Unity, Unity,
who am I talking to?
I watched you assimilate a
whole police station
just to get your hands on the
evidence locker.
Rick, when we met,
I was a young hive mind
with the population
of a small town.
People change...
[engine turns over]
Especially when I change them.
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but I've grown.
Hey, listen, I've grown, too.
I have!
See, I've I've reconnected
with my family, right?
Hm. Why's that, I wonder?
Maybe it's part of getting old.
Maybe I just missed being with
a collective.
[Moaning]
ALL: Yes, Rick. Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Yes. Yes.
Wait, wait. Stop.
Hold it.
Not like this.
We need a hang glider and a
crotchless uncle Sam costume,
and I want the entire field of
your largest stadium
covered end to end
with naked redheads,
and I want the stands packed
with every man that remotely
resembles my father.
[Triumphant music plays]
Man, look at them go.
So coordinated.
[Gulps]
What's your problem?
They're making you into a
Mount Rushmore.
They made burgers!
Morty, open your eyes.
There is no "they".
These poor people's
bodies are being used.
They're a planet of puppets.
- I can hear you.
- Ugh.
Well, it seems like everybody
here's cool with it.
Except for all those redheads.
They seem like they're in a
hurry to be somewhere else.
Balloon, Summer?
Balloon, Morty?
No, we don't want your
dumb balloons, okay?
We're bored.
Take us back to Rick.
Now's not a good time.
Oh, yeah!
I want yooooooou!
ALL: [Chanting] Go, son, go!
Go, son, go!
Oh, real nice.
Real nice.
How does a man do this
without me noticing?
Oh, you know my dad once he
puts his mind to something.
You're spinning
this to his credit?
[Screeching, gurgling]
I'm going down there.
- Jerry--
- Beth, this is my house,
which makes this my garage,
my secret hatch,
my hidden subterranean lair,
and my faceless gargler.
Now, are you gonna
keep hating this playa
or are you gonna
jack my steez?
Okay, you're just
making stuff up now.
[Applause] Ugh. Oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
Ugh!
[Glug! Glug! Glug!]
Oh, Rick.
That was so bad.
What's this "was" stuff?
I just need to hydrate,
then we're doing that again.
[Spaceships whir]
- Oh, damn.
- Listen, if this is an invasion,
I got to sit this one out,
but I'll be back to have sex
with the survivors.
It's a neighboring hive-mind
species, beta seven.
Our planets maintain a
practical alliance
for exchange of vital resources,
so be nice.
Unity, is it a bad time?
Are all present life forms
assimilated?
Beta seven, this is my single-minded
friend from Earth, Rick.
Rick Sanchez.
Unity has spoken of you.
All bad, I hope.
Ha ha!
ALL: Bleeeeeeeeeh!
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Beta seven, if my allies
are a problem for you,
perhaps our alliance is,
as well.
Our alliance is beneficial.
When beta seven expresses concern,
it's only because--
Oh, snap!
Powdered neutronium?
Amphetetron?
You know I can make
with this stuff?
Oh, Rick, I-- I shouldn't.
Come on.
It's not every day that I'm town.
It's for old time's sake.
Uh...
Okay, what the hell.
We can purify the resin and
make fractal dust.
Oh, I was thinking
velocitinis, but--
Aw, old man Rick can't party
with a whole planet?
[Both laugh]
I can do whatever you do and
more, baby.
[All groaning]
You know, I think [belches]
beta seven over there
is hoping your alliance can be
more than practical.
[Laughing]
Stop.
[Laughter]
Well, this explains
the $6,000 electric bill.
Whoa!
[Screeches]
Well, nice.
Real nice.
Alien prisoners
under the house.
Real nice.
Nice. Reeeeeeeeeeeeeal--
God damn it, stop.
Wake up, people!
You have to fight it!
You're under the spell of an
evil monster!
- I can hear you.
- Yeah, so you keep saying.
[Grunts]
- Summer!
- Wake up!
You have to have some
individuality left in there!
Why do you hate me, Summer?
I'm not talking you.
I'm talking to...
Steven Phillips.
Steven, set yourself free.
Summer, before I took over
this planet,
this man was a registered sex
offender.
Yeah? Well, so what?
At least he was himself.
This woman was a drug addict
on the verge of suicide.
Now she's a marine biologist.
Listen, Unity, I don't think
my sister's trying to say
that life would be perfect
without you.
I think she's just saying that
life would be, you know, life.
I have transformed life here
into a paradise.
Prostitutes are now scientists.
The homeless are now
"phisosophers".
Oh. Oh. "Ph-phisosophers"?
Nice.
- Philopol... phiphophopher...
- Oh, my god.
Where did you learn to talk,
you grandpa-stealing slut?
I'm feeling...
[Retches]
Ugh.
Oh, man, let me help all of
you guys up.
ALL: I'm fine.
[Dance music plays]
[Sniffs] Do you know what I
love about you, Rick?
You're the only
single mind I've met
that really sees
the big picture.
You got that right.
But, baby, listen
y-you're talking about taking
over planets and galaxies.
You got to just remember to
let go sometimes, you know?
I can let go.
Hey, look.
You see that town
across the river?
Watch this.
- Whoa!
- Ha ha! Whoo!
Whoa!
That's not what I meant!
[Laughing] It's okay.
It's okay.
I evacuated.
I evacuated the town. Look.
ALL: Hey! We're right here.
We're fine.
[Laughs]
Oh, that was awesome.
[Chuckles]
My my grandkids weren't in
that town, right?
A-are my grandkids alive?
M-my drink is empty.
[All retching]
[Groans]
♪ ♪
- Unity, what's happening?
- Who's Unity?
You kids have nice feet.
Mind if I take a picture?
Gross. No.
[Cellphone camera clicks]
Morty: I think you're getting
what you wanted, Summer.
Something's happening to Unity.
Do all of you
remember who you are?
Yeah, uh, my name
is Ron Benson.
I'm an electrical engineer,
father of two,
and, as you can see from my flat,
concentric nipple rings,
I'm a member of this
planet's top race!
[Cheers]
Okay, that's good.
Uh, don't focus too much on
the last part, but--
I'm Daryl Jefferson.
I'm a landscaper.
And I'll be damned if
that ripple-nipple bitch's
race is superior!
The cone-nipple people will
rule this world!
You shut your mouth, you dirty
knife-nipple bastards.
What'd you say to me,
you target-chest piece of [bleep]?
Race war!
Ugh!
[Grunting]
Why are you fighting?!
Can't you see you're all the same?
Oh, Summer.
[Laughs]
First race war, huh?
[All shouting, screaming]
Way to go, Summer.
You started a race war.
I didn't start it!
They're the racists.
I merely empowered them to follow
their apparently misguided dreams.
Okay, thanks for clarifying.
I'll have a super-accurate
headstone now.
Hey, wait what
race are you guys?
We're neither.
S-see?
Yeah, take my word for it.
We just have regular nipples.
Hey, these two
freaks have no race!
♪ ♪
[All shouting indistinctly]
Oh, there's no place like home.
There's no place like home.
Remember, Summer?
- From Dorothy and the tiny people movie?
- Yes, yes.
- All the tiny people.
- Dorothy, take us away.
♪ ♪
Hello, Summer.
Hello, Morty.
- It's okay. You're safe now.
- Unity?
- Yes.
- Oh, Unity, I am so sorry.
I didn't know freedom meant
people doing stuff that sucks.
I was thinking more of
a choose your own
cellphone-carrier thing.
Oh, Summer, you did
nothing wrong.
I'm having fun with your
grandpa.
Lost a little control.
Probably shouldn't be piloting
a hovercopter,
nor should I be running
200,000 pediatric hospitals
and 12 million deep fryers,
but hey, it's not like this planet
can take its business elsewhere.
Um, should we maybe stop
somewhere and get you a coffee?
Maybe splash a little water on
your face, or...
No, no, if I wanted to be sober,
I wouldn't have gotten drunk.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
[Screeches, gurgles]
Oh, man.
I cannot wait--
I cannot wait to hear Rick
explain his way around this.
He is gone.
Jerry, stop, please, okay?
We weren't even supposed
to be down here.
If we confront him about this--
Oh, my god!
I love this.
I love that this is how far
you will go for him.
You want to go upstairs
and cut carrots
and watch a Lifetime original
above a [bleep] alien dungeon!
Your relationship with your
father is psychotic.
Oh, listen to you
relish the idea
that my genius father
is a bad person.
Step out of your
ego for a second
and look at this thing;
it's a monster.
He might have it chained up
so that it doesn't eat the planet!
Right, because your father's
such an altruist?
I once saw him briefly forget
the word for "humans".
He's probably harvesting this
creature's organs.
He's probably racing to cure
its space AIDS.
- He's going to eat it!
- He's protecting it!
[Shrills]
- Shut up!
[Humming]
Whoa!
Unity, this place is a mess.
Oh, it's cool.
The part of me that's the cleaning
lady is coming on Friday.
[Gasps] Oh, my god.
I have a meeting
at the Galactic Federation
in an hour.
Oh, I'll never make it.
Ah, I'll push it to next week.
Unity, could you get
Rick out here, please?
He's unavailable.
He's...
Having sex with you.
We get it. Gross.
Get him out here now.
I don't think he wants to be--
- Grandpa Rick!
- Rick! Rick!
I'm gonna tell mom and dad
about the gagoo
you have locked up
under the garage!
[Belches] What the hell is
your problem?
Grandpa, we need
to go home, now.
Fine. Sheesh.
[Glass shatters]
[Beeps]
See you.
Uh, Rick, I think
we should allgo.
Tend to your garden, kids.
I'm kind of doing a thing here.
[Laughs] Whoo!
Grandpa Rick, we're not
leaving without you.
Oh, my god, you guys.
I get it.
You're afraid the big,
bad hive mind
is gonna steal
your grandpa away.
Actually, no.
I think Unity's great and you're
a horrible influence on it.
- What?
- This isn't healthy, Rick.
You know, you're really
up to no good
around here a-at this place,
you know?
You and Unity are like...
like leggings and mid-calf boots.
You think you're great together,
but you're just bringing out
the worst in each other.
Oh, gee.
Boy, Summer. Well put.
Uh, why don't we see
what Unity thinks?
Unity?
I'm just taking a little break
from stuff.
You know?
I need to relax.
Oh, hey, w-what's this on the
news, guys?
Let me turn it up.
In the news today,
this looks a lot worse than it is.
We're really just having a
good time.
- Karen?
- Thanks, Todd.
Up next, are you a concerned
grandchild or just a buzzkill?
We'll tell you how you can
know for sure.
I think you two are a little
outnumbered.
Okay, well, what if
you did it for me?
What if you came with us as a
favor to us because you love us?
What?
Dumb. Bye.
But Rick, Summer's just---
Summer's just a
hyper-emotional, needy little--
What's the word I'm
looking for here?
Uh... Human.
It runs in the family.
I can tolerate it,
but I can't give a crap about it.
Take a hike.
Take care of yourself, Unity.
I'm not looking for judgment,
just a yes or no...
can you assimilate a giraffe?
- You're the worst!
- No, you're the worst!
You don't support this family!
All you care about is yourself!
- is about supporting you emotionally...
- You've got two children...
- ...but you're unsupportable.
- ...Being dragged across the cosmos...
- ...because it's never enough, Jerry!
- ...By your dangerously ill father!
And you force me to watch it happen because
you'd rather lose them and lose me...
And you don't even know what it's like to be
afraid of losing anything ...Than lose him!
- Because you cling and you cling
- Because you're the child, Beth!
You, not me! You!
[Screeches]
- Aah!
- Oh, my god.
[Both sigh]
[Both gasp]
Um, first of all, hello.
Uh, my name is Blim Blam the
Korblok.
Second of all, cards
on the table,
I'm a murderer that eats babies,
and I came to this planet to
eat babies.
However, I am also carrying a
highly infectious disease
that I suppose you could call
"space AIDS" as you put it.
And Rick did chain me up so that
he could attempt to cure it.
At the same time,
Rick's motivation
to cure my disease
was not to save my life or
anyone else's,
but to patent and sell the cure
for billions of blemflarcks.
But you know the reason why I
ripped my chains out of the wall?
And do you know why I'm never
coming back to this planet?
Because the two of you
are the [bleep] worst!
You both hate yourselves
and each other.
And the idea that it has anything
to do with Rick is laughable.
I'd laugh,
but I'm biologically incapable.
That's how alien I am.
And even I'm sitting here
listening to the two of you
and being like,
"What the [beep]"?
So good luck with
your shitty marriage,
and tell Rick I'm sorry he has
to deal with either of you.
Blim Blam out.
[Gurgles]
You know what?
I'm taking this.
How do you--
What is this?
Uh, is there a slow setting?
Best door ever.
Rick:
[Belches, sighs, coughs]
Okay, okay. Now make them cry,
but happy crying.
Now make them all make fun of
the blonde one.
Now make them all
do it on the table.
I can't believe you created a
whole show for me.
Now cancel it.
Okay, now put it back on.
[Laughs]
All right, I'm bored.
Rick, is there a way for you
to call Summer and Morty?
- I feel bad that they--
- Pbht. Screw those guys.
Ugh. I'll be right back.
Don't waste your brain on
those weirdos, Unity.
They're no different from any of the
aimless chumps that you occupy.
They just put you at the center of
their lives because you're powerful.
And then because
they put you there,
they want you to
be less powerful.
Never gonna happen though,
right?
ALL: Never.
Never.
Back in a flash.
[Door whooshes]
[Toilet flushes]
Best weekend ever, Rick.
I agree, Rick. Let's see how
long we can go.
Hey, Une.
You got any more--
Female president: Rick, forgive
me for doing this in notes.
I'm not strong enough to do it
in persons.
Delivery guy: I realize now
that I'm attracted to you
for the same reason I
can't be with you.
You can't change.
Beggar: And I have no problem
with that,
but it clearly means I have a
problem with myself.
Newspaper vendor: I'm sure there's
no perfect version of me.
I'm sure I'll just unify
species after species
and never really be complete.
Female president: But I know
how it goes with us.
I lose who I am and become
part of you.
Because in a strange way,
you're better at what I do
without even trying.
Yours, and nobody else's, Unity.
P.S., I don't know where those
coal miners were
before they were assimilated.
You might want to get checked.
MAN: [Belches] [Laughter]
[Door opens, closes]
Hey.
Dad.
[Clears throat]
I, um Jerry and I
were looking for
our weed whacker
and found your subterranean lair
and your alien prisoner,
and he got away.
And I know I sound like mom,
but I can't sacrifice this
whole family's safety
just because I'm afraid you'll
leave again,
so no more alien prisoners
and no more subterranean
excavation without consulting us.
- Okay.
- Okay?
"Okay" like you're gonna
quietly teleport somewhere
- and never come back?
- No. It's your house.
Grandpa Rick, what happened
with Unity?
Who? Oh, Unity.
Yeah, well...
I mean, honestly, we're
talking about an entity
that thrives on enslavement,
you know?
It's not cool.
Fun's fun, but who needs it?
I'll be in the garage.
[Chaos Chaos's "Do You Feel It?" Plays]
♪ Lay it, lay it down ♪
♪ Let me see your hand ♪
♪ Show me what you got ♪
♪ You're always talking ♪
♪ But you're not playing ♪
♪ It doesn't match your face ♪
♪ Get them away,
away from this place ♪
♪ Can you take me now? ♪
♪ I, I want it ♪
♪ I want it real ♪
♪ Are you afraid of me now? ♪
♪
[Machine whirring]
♪ Are you afraid of me now? ♪
♪ Do you feel it? ♪
♪ Do you feel that I can see
your soul? ♪
♪ Do you feel it? ♪
♪ Do you feel the pain in
your heart? ♪
♪ I, I want it ♪
♪ I want it real ♪
♪ Run away with me now ♪
♪ I, I want it ♪
♪ I want it real ♪
♪ Run away with me now ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Don't leave me ♪
♪ Never leave me out ♪
Rick: Unity! Unity!
Unity!
How can I assist you?
I want to talk to [Belches]
Unity, beta seven.
I know it's in there.
You're classified as
a hostile entity,
and Unity doesn't
want to talk to you.
I know your game, beta seven.
I've met a billion of you,
you little on-deck, in-the-wings
shoulder to cry on!
You are classified
as a hostile entity.
Oh, you're just loving this,
mother--
This isn't gonna shake out
like you think, pal.
Unity's not into
other hive minds.
It's gonna suck you
in and use you up,
and a month from now,
I'm gonna be making out with all
of you in a bunch of red wigs!
Unity! Unity!
Unity, I know you can hear me.
Get out here.
Weapons systems engaged.
Oh, in your dreams you have
weapon systems.
Ugh, Rick, you said we were
going to a movie.
We are, Morty.
All right, beta shit seven,
you just got saved by the
bell, bitch!
[Screaming]
MAN: Did you get any of that?
MAN: It's-a good show-a.
Sync and corrections by XhmikosR
www.addic7ed.com